export const iaResponse1 = {
  exam: [
    {
      questionType: 'Vocabulary',
      content: {
        questions: [
          {
            question:
              'What is the name of the historic event that led to the creation of the UN?',
            answer: 'The Second World War',
            alternatives: ['The Cold War', 'The First World War'],
          },
          {
            question:
              'What was the name of the conference that led to the creation of the UN? It was held in San Francisco.',
            answer:
              'The United Nations Conference on International Organization',
            alternatives: [
              'The San Francisco Conference',
              'The Chicago Conference',
            ],
          },
          {
            question:
              'What was the name of the document that was signed at the United Nations Conference on International Organization? It was signed by 50 nations on 26 June 1945.',
            answer: 'The United Nations Charter',
            alternatives: [
              'The San Francisco Charter',
              'The United Nations Treaty',
            ],
          },
          {
            question:
              'In what language was the United Nations Charter written? And who wrote the preamble of the Charter?',
            answer:
              'The Charter was written in the English language. The Preamble was written by the American Committee, and it was included in the final draft by the vote of the U.N. Conference on International Organization.',
            alternatives: ['The French language', 'The Russian language'],
          },
          {
            question:
              'Where is the United Nations Charter written? It was written in the White House.',
            answer:
              'The United Nations Charter was written in the United States of America.',
            alternatives: ['The United Kingdom', 'The Soviet Union'],
          },
        ],
      },
    },
    {
      questionType: 'Translation',
      content: {
        questions: [
          {
            question:
              'The Earth is the only planet to have life. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo es el unico planeta con vida. Es verdad o falso',
          },
          {
            question: 'The Earth is a round shaped planet. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo es un planeta en forma de pelota. Es verdad o falso',
          },
          {
            question: 'The Earth is located in the Solar System. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo está en el Sistema Solar. Es verdad o falso',
          },
          {
            question: 'The Earth has one Moon. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo tiene un solo Moon. Es verdad o falso',
          },
          {
            question: 'The Earth is a part of the Milky Way. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo forma parte de la galaxia Milky Way. Es verdad o falso',
          },
        ],
      },
    },
    {
      questionType: 'FillInTheBlank',
      content: {
        questions: [
          {
            question:
              'The Big Bang theory is the prevailing cosmological model for the observable universe. The model is based on the idea that the universe expanded from a ______________ state of extremely high temperature and density, and continues to expand today.',
            answer: 'singularity',
            alternatives: ['', ' Galaxies ', ' Stars ', ' Planets '],
          },
          {
            question:
              'The expansion of the universe is an ongoing process that began with the Big Bang. The expansion of the universe is causing the ____________ between galaxies to increase.',
            answer: 'redshift',
            alternatives: ['', ' blueshift ', ' lightyears ', ' parsecs '],
          },
          {
            question:
              'Active galaxies are ___________ galaxies that have supermassive black holes at their centers.',
            answer: 'galaxies',
            alternatives: ['', ' clusters ', ' stars ', ' planets '],
          },
          {
            question:
              'A supermassive black hole is a black hole with a mass that is _______________ a million solar masses.',
            answer: 'at least',
            alternatives: ['', ' more than ', ' less than ', ' equal to '],
          },
          {
            question:
              'The Hawking radiation is a thermal spectrum of electromagnetic radiation emitted by ______________.',
            answer: 'black holes',
            alternatives: ['', ' stars ', ' galaxies ', ' planets '],
          },
        ],
      },
    },
  ],
};

export const iaResponse2 = {
  exam: [
    {
      questionType: 'Vocabulary',
      content: {
        questions: [
          {
            question:
              'What is the name of the historic event that led to the creation of the UN?',
            answer: 'The Second World War',
            alternatives: ['The Cold War', 'The First World War'],
          },
          {
            question:
              'What was the name of the conference that led to the creation of the UN? It was held in San Francisco.',
            answer:
              'The United Nations Conference on International Organization',
            alternatives: [
              'The San Francisco Conference',
              'The Chicago Conference',
            ],
          },
          {
            question:
              'What was the name of the document that was signed at the United Nations Conference on International Organization? It was signed by 50 nations on 26 June 1945.',
            answer: 'The United Nations Charter',
            alternatives: [
              'The San Francisco Charter',
              'The United Nations Treaty',
            ],
          },
          {
            question:
              'In what language was the United Nations Charter written? And who wrote the preamble of the Charter?',
            answer:
              'The Charter was written in the English language. The Preamble was written by the American Committee, and it was included in the final draft by the vote of the U.N. Conference on International Organization.',
            alternatives: ['The French language', 'The Russian language'],
          },
          {
            question:
              'Where is the United Nations Charter written? It was written in the White House.',
            answer:
              'The United Nations Charter was written in the United States of America.',
            alternatives: ['The United Kingdom', 'The Soviet Union'],
          },
        ],
      },
    },
    {
      questionType: 'Translation',
      content: {
        questions: [
          {
            question:
              'The Earth is the only planet to have life. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo es el unico planeta con vida. Es verdad o falso',
          },
          {
            question: 'The Earth is a round shaped planet. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo es un planeta en forma de pelota. Es verdad o falso',
          },
          {
            question: 'The Earth is located in the Solar System. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo está en el Sistema Solar. Es verdad o falso',
          },
          {
            question: 'The Earth has one Moon. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo tiene un solo Moon. Es verdad o falso',
          },
          {
            question: 'The Earth is a part of the Milky Way. True or False',
            questionTranslated:
              'El mundo forma parte de la galaxia Milky Way. Es verdad o falso',
          },
        ],
      },
    },
    {
      questionType: 'FillInTheBlank',
      content: {
        questions: [
          {
            question:
              'The Big Bang theory is the prevailing cosmological model for the observable universe. The model is based on the idea that the universe expanded from a ______________ state of extremely high temperature and density, and continues to expand today.',
            answer: 'singularity',
            alternatives: ['', ' Galaxies ', ' Stars ', ' Planets '],
          },
          {
            question:
              'The expansion of the universe is an ongoing process that began with the Big Bang. The expansion of the universe is causing the ____________ between galaxies to increase.',
            answer: 'redshift',
            alternatives: ['', ' blueshift ', ' lightyears ', ' parsecs '],
          },
          {
            question:
              'Active galaxies are ___________ galaxies that have supermassive black holes at their centers.',
            answer: 'galaxies',
            alternatives: ['', ' clusters ', ' stars ', ' planets '],
          },
          {
            question:
              'A supermassive black hole is a black hole with a mass that is _______________ a million solar masses.',
            answer: 'at least',
            alternatives: ['', ' more than ', ' less than ', ' equal to '],
          },
          {
            question:
              'The Hawking radiation is a thermal spectrum of electromagnetic radiation emitted by ______________.',
            answer: 'black holes',
            alternatives: ['', ' stars ', ' galaxies ', ' planets '],
          },
        ],
      },
    },
  ],
};
